<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Business Challenge</string>
    <string name="blank">No Information</string>
    <string name="detail_error_message">Business data not available</string>
    <string name="action_close">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="unlock_previous">View previous day first and wait for 24hours to unlock this day</string>
    <string name="start_challenge">Start Challenge</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>

    <string-array name="business_days">
        <item>Day 1</item>
        <item>Day 2</item>
        <item>Day 3</item>
        <item>Day 4</item>
        <item>Day 5</item>
        <item>Day 6</item>
        <item>Day 7</item>
        <item>Day 8</item>
        <item>Day 9</item>
        <item>Day 10</item>
        <item>Day 11</item>
        <item>Day 12</item>
        <item>Day 13</item>
        <item>Day 14</item>
        <item>Day 15</item>
        <item>Day 16</item>
        <item>Day 17</item>
        <item>Day 18</item>
        <item>Day 19</item>
        <item>Day 20</item>
        <item>Day 21</item>
        <item>Day 22</item>
        <item>Day 23</item>
        <item>Day 24</item>
        <item>Day 25</item>
        <item>Day 26</item>
        <item>Day 27</item>
        <item>Day 28</item>
        <item>Day 29</item>
        <item>Day 30</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="business_details">
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 1\"},\"description\":\"First thing’s first!
            You don’t want to waste time trying to build something someone has already
            tried (or succeeded) to create! Take this first day and look through the
            filed patents. You may need some help with combing through everything.
            There are U.S. Patent libraries in many states, but you can also search online.
            Once you pass your preliminary search, you can hire a professional to look more
            in-depth, depending on what you
            find.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/HAXxmFI.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 2\"},\"description\":\"Do you have a business plan?
            If not, start doing some research and write up a rough draft for one today.
            We’ll come back to it in a few days to refine
            it.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/wcSdJdj.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 3\"},\"description\":\"You’ll want to protect your
        ideas for the future. Look into trademarking, copyrighting, patenting, and so forth
        concerning your intellectual property and don’t forget to look into intellectual
        property insurance. It may sound silly or like something you don’t need but,
        if you don’t have that insurance and someone walks off with your idea and puts
        their name on it, it becomes theirs solely in the eyes of the law, and
        you may lose your
        shirt.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/6cdlV7L.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 4\"},\"description\":\"Decide which business format
            is right for you. Today should focus on research into the different types of business
            registrations. S and C corporations, Limited Liability Company (LLC), and Limited
            Company (Ltd) are just a few examples of the different types of business formats that
            help protect you and your assets if something ever happens with the company. There are
            also differences in how the business and you are taxed throughout the year depending
            on which format you chose.
    If you don’t already have a unique name for your business, today would be a good day to
            work on that. Don’t forget your elevator pitch! This pitch would be a 10-30 second
            ad for your product or service that you could give to someone on an elevator ride.
            Let your mind do most of the work today. Remember: Rome wasn’t built in a day and
            your business won’t be
            either!\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/6cdlV7L.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 5\"},\"description\":\"Now that you’ve looked into your
            intellectual property being insured, and what kind of business will work best for you,
            it wouldn’t be a bad idea to get some insurance for your actual company.
            This insurance can include but is not limited to, inventory, any physical space you
            do your work, vehicles used, even self and employee
            coverage.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/6CpJ1er.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 6\"},\"description\":\"Today you can start setting
            up the face of your business. Do you have a logo? If not and you have the skills,
            try creating a few today. Choose a color pallet and a mascot if one is appropriate.
            Try writing the name of your business in different handwriting, block letters or
            script, and working the logo into the handwritten signature. If you are not
            artistically inclined, do a quick search for graphic designers in your area to help you
            out.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/6cdlV7L.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 7\"},\"description\":\"If you need some help getting
            your product from concept to tangible, today you should find a local prototype
            designer such as Beyond Design Inc. in Chicago or Kaleidoscope Innovation Product
            Design And Development in Cincinnati. Once you have a physical prototype, come back
            to the challenge and pick up here.
If you already have a prototype or are providing a service, set up some beta testing today.
            Get a few folks to try it out and give you their feedback. Start to identify your
            weak points and figure out possible
            solutions.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/U7km7CZ.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 8\"},\"description\":\"Today you should make sure your
            product or service is complete. It’s better to have something that is finished that
            something perfect; changes will come along the way. Take your product through its
            functions. Make sure that, when you get to the end, you’re where you want to be.
If you’re providing a service, run through the entire process start to finish and make sure you
            have everything you need for every step. Touch everything you will need. If you make
            a mental note to get something, you may not have its opening
            day.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/6cdlV7L.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 9\"},\"description\":\"While you’re looking into the
            legal side of things, make sure you don’t need any permits or licensure.
            Even online businesses can be subject to specific licensing and regulatory practices.
            It’s also not a bad idea to check and see if your business might qualify for a tax
            exemption.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/MNxGFIe.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 10\"},\"description\":\"Come back to your business plan.
            Read through it. Do you still agree with everything? If not, make changes to it today
            and begin to implement those changes. If everything still measures up, go through
            it with a fine-toothed comb and make sure you’re set up to meet all of your
            goals.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/6cdlV7L.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 11\"},\"description\":\"If you don’t already have the
            funds to start your new venture, look into getting a business loan and credit card.
            Make a list of potential investors and look into crowdsourcing. Go ahead and set up
            any online sources you
            can.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/vsqkaTq.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 12\"},\"description\":\"If you’ve never worked in sales,
            take today to watch a few videos online and read a few articles about selling
            yourself and your product or service. Practice in front of a mirror, film yourself
            and watch it back. Have a friend help advise you. They may see something that you miss.
            Pitch to them, practice, practice, practice! Soon it will become second
            nature.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/6cdlV7L.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 13\"},\"description\":\"Use today to research pitch
            decks. These, in brief, are typically PowerPoints with 10-12 slides that you might
            send digitally or present in person to new potential investors. There are several
            references on do’s and don’ts out there. With a brief online search, you will find
            one you can utilize. Once you find one you like, go ahead and work on this
            presentation.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/6cdlV7L.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 14\"},\"description\":\"Have a friend over to work on
            your pitch deck today. Again, film yourself and watch it replayed. If you have a
            large screen or a blank wall to project onto, set your camera up at an investor
            and pitch to it. Have your partner help you find and correct the weak
            points.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/6cdlV7L.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 15\"},\"description\":\"If you plan on having
            investors in your business that are not business partners, do some research today
            on the different kinds of investors and which type might be best for you.
            If you find something that looks promising, do a few web searches. Many investors
            specialize in a field, and you may find someone who would be just the right fit.
            Check out the “pitch decks” on day Piktochart before reaching
            out.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/6cdlV7L.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 16\"},\"description\":\"Before you launch, it is
            crucial to have your finances straight! Make today about getting your tax ID and
            checking on bookkeeping and accounting. If you have employees, they will need
            to be paid promptly. If you have suppliers or shipping costs, those bills can
            pile up quickly and sneakily. Moreover, everyone knows Uncle Sam will come after
            you if you don’t pay the
            piper!\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/6cdlV7L.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 17\"},\"description\":\"Write up some contracts today
            or hire someone to do that for you. You will need an agreement between you and your
            employees if you have any, you may need a contract between you and your
            clients depending on what your services are, you might want to consider an agreement
            between you and a long term supplier, and, if you have any investors,
            you’ll want one for them,
            too.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/0eTLBHD.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 18\"},\"description\":\"If you have business partners,
            take today to sit down with them and work out how you will split up the assets
            and what will be fair for everyone. Have a blank contract where you can write in
            the agreement or be prepared to create one today and have everyone sign
            it.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/6cdlV7L.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 19\"},\"description\":\"Do some research on your
            competition today. Who are they? Are they in the same industry as you or is it a
            similar product? What do you like about the way they do things and is there any way
            to put a positive spin on that to benefit you? What weaknesses do you see? Do you
            have any of the same flaws and can you correct
            them?\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/6cdlV7L.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 20\"},\"description\":\"INVENTORY! You need to have
            THINGS! If you are selling a product, stock up now! Make as many as you can hold;
            make at least two of everything. If people want something and you don’t have it as
            soon as you open, they may not come back again to check for it despite e-mails,
            text reminders, and the like. If you are selling a service, print off some coupons
            today. Have them on hand to either give your customers directly when performing
            the service or sent in an e-mail after. If you have a physical storefront, get a
            display stand and place your coupons somewhere folks can see it.
            They may try you out if they “get a good deal” the first
            time.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/6cdlV7L.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 21\"},\"description\":\"One of the most sorely
            overlooked and misused marketing tools in our society today is social media.
            It is essential that you can connect with your public on these platforms.
            Depending on your product you may need to utilize the top three. These are Facebook,
            Twitter, and Instagram. Instagram is more photo heavy so if you don’t have a very
            visual product, Twitter and Facebook are probably your best bet. Take today to set
            up the accounts for your business with them. There are business tools on both that
            you can familiarize yourself with as you
            go.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/U8qjkEn.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 22\"},\"description\":\"Picture day! You will need
            visual aids for your pitch desk, business cards and advertising, website, storefront,
            and social media accounts. If you enjoy taking pictures, go out and take some around
            town. Local flavor, recognizable landmarks, and unique images from around town always
            resonate with residents and will encourage a warm beginning to your relationship
            with them. If you don’t take your own pictures, consider searching for a local
            photographer who may already have some images you could buy or search for images in
            the public domain online. Be sure you have the right to use them. If they are
            copyrighted and the proper permission/citations aren’t given, you could wind up in
            some hot water
            legally.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/6cdlV7L.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 23\"},\"description\":\"If you have the skills to
            build your website, do that today. If you don’t have those skills,
            use today to check out some competitors’ sites and find a couple of things you like.
            Then find someone who has the skills you need and show them your examples. They will
            build you a straightforward site and then you will be able to go through it with them
            to tweak and
            change.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/6cdlV7L.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 24\"},\"description\":\"Content Creation Day!
            Creating content can be “leg day” for your brain but don’t let it overwhelm you.
            Today you will need to focus on what you want to present to your customers.
            If you have a physical store, what is your style? Do you have a theme? Can you
            incorporate your logo, color pallet, or business name into your décor?
            If your store is strictly online or, if you have a website where you will sell also,
            you need to consider the same things while additionally creating written content
            for your site.
Again, don’t let this overwhelm you. You likely don’t need much. Write the essential information
            in a bulleted list and then turn your list into a short paragraph.
            If it gets to be too much, consider hiring a freelancer.
            They do that kind of thing for
            fun.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/6cdlV7L.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 25\"},\"description\":\"If you are a confident public
            speaker, take today to write some brain teasers to help you with your pitch deck.
            If you struggle with public speaking, get some friends together in a comfortable but
            public place, such as a coffee shop or college commons, and give them your pitch.
            Then, do it again. And again. The best way to become a confident public speaker,
            which you will have to do at some point during your growth, is to practice speaking
            to a familiar group in
            public.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/ZtRspU2.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 26\"},\"description\":\"Up to this point, we have
            focused a lot on the internal workings of, and start-up aspect for, your business.
            Now let’s look outward. What about your customers? Make a list of demographics today.
            Who is your target audience? Where are they located? How do they get a hold of you?
            Do you have/want/need a business phone/phone number? How about e-mail address or
            physical address? Throughout the day, think about how you have contacted businesses
            similar to your own and what you like the
            best.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/6cdlV7L.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 27\"},\"description\":\"You’re getting close to your
            launch, now! Start thinking about marketing. Where will your services be most helpful?
            Where would your product be most used? Would a flier be an appropriate method of
            marketing? How about a poster or a billboard? Do you have any online ads and whom
            would you like to show these? Do you have business cards? There are hundreds of
            different methods of advertising. Take today to look at your demographic and potential
            client base and think about the best way to reach
            them.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/6cdlV7L.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 28\"},\"description\":\"Research places that will help
            you create advertisements and get them where you need them. If you can do this yourself,
            take today and print off your fliers or call in your billboard. Hit the bricks on this
            one and start getting your word out there! A handwritten launch date on your cards and
            leaflets can add a warm, personal
            touch.\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/6cdlV7L.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 29\"},\"description\":\"Before you open,
            make sure you are ready for your customers. Have a pre-opening test run with a few friends
            or partners and have them try to find weaknesses. If you can, correct these.
            If they are simply the way things are, create an action plan for how to deal with the issue
            when it arises, as it almost certainly
            will\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/6cdlV7L.jpg\"}
        </item>
        <item>{\"name\":{\"mainName\":\"Day 30\"},\"description\":\"Congratulations! You’ve completed the challenge and are ready to open your doors!
            Good luck!\",\"image\":\"https://i.imgur.com/6cdlV7L.jpg\"}
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
